Manager Tota
She is our new staff member
It's my first day in the Marketing Department
My name is Saya Amami
Good morning
Good morning, Manager
It's the documents you need
Did we really
You meant I was lying?
I don't blame you for not remembering it
We really didn't have any relationship before
Go home quickly if possible
I can't refuse him
(See you at Resource Room at 6p.m. Tota.)
Ignore him. Go home
Sawako
Don't ever set your feet in the room again
What have you done to my wife?
Did you send her the photo?
I didn't
The photo is what I use to bait you
How'd I easily let if off?
Stop pretending. You're a subversive
You'd hate the ones who was cruel to your mom
It has nothing to do with my family
How'd you say so?
You don't get the aim and the stance
I've had enough of you
Would your mom be happy with what you do?
Manager, what're you doing?
Don't you forget what kind of place the office is?
Hey, Kadokura
Did you know why Saori Amami
didn't go to the Alumni gathering?
It's said she couldn't move around
She's taken care of by her daughter
Really?
Why do you keep asking about Amami recently?
Sorry, I'll talk to you later
Hey
Let me see Amami
I want to talk to your mom personally
Is she home?
I didn't expect your visit
Amami, it's Tota
Please come in
In there
20 years ago, she died after
having given birth to me
She only left with me these diaries
She'd been writing diaries
Maybe Tota likes me too
How'd I tell him I love him?
God, how'd I get pregnant
as a result of being raped?
I really want to see Tota
Let's write a letter to tell him
I want to see him
If he doesn't show up, I'll forget about him
But if he comes...
Mom died on the day you're supposed to meet
It's said she neglected the traffic light
She must be in great despair then
She wouldn't have died if you had shown up
Why didn't you show up?
Did you receive the letter?
Tota
I'm scared
I'm really scared
What do you mean?
I'd been loving her
After we met at the medical room,
she withdrew from the school suddenly
I still loved her after I went to university
and I joined the society
I had always wanted to forget her
I thought I couldn't find one
who I loved as much as I loved her
Why didn't you show up then?
I don't know
I didn't know she loved me too
She didn't say so in the letter
I was scared
I was afraid she'd know I loved her
So was mom
She was scared too
Chicken
Mom
Is that good enough?
Are you alright?
Mr Hayakawa
I was shopping and forgot about the time
You came here for grocery?
Are you alright?
I'm home
Where's mom?
Have you had dinner yet?
Mom doesn't come home, it's all your fault
Want 1 more can?
I've had enough
Momoko is left alone at home. It's worrying
You live in such a big house alone?
Right. But I'm still feel bad to
have dinner alone
What do your parents do?
I'm an orphan
I grew up in an orphanage
Really?
I don't usually talk about it
I don't need sympathy
You're strong, Mr Hayakawa
Not at all
You're very strong
Because I like you, Ms Sawako
Strange? I must be drunk
I like Mr Hayakawa too
I'll have to count on you for teaching Momoko.
Let me walk you to the station
No, thanks. See you
Hey
It's you? I told you not to call me again
Forget it. You go home with your husband
Please, just 1 last time
I can't forget the time we spent in the secret room
Shingo, please
I don't care, stupid
Ridiculous
Nonsense
Sawako
You still haven't gone to bed yet?
Where have you been?
Makoto, do you regret having married me?
I was recommend by your boss,
and you could reject it?
Not really
That's impossible
Manager, you got a minute?
What's the matter?
It's about Kubo Fabric, can we talk?
Oh?
And
I have something personal to talk with you,
let's have dinner together tonight
I'll make the reservation. Excuse me
Tsuboi
I'm sorry, I'm late
Do you feel lonely without your dad here, Momoko?
No, I feel happier with you here
Momoko
Mom and Dad sleep in different rooms now
Stop the nonsense, and eat
Can I stay longer before your husband returns?
Oh?
Of course, let's play video games together
Momoko
I want to say hi to your husband too
I've always respected you, Manager
I think you take all the credits of
the success in our work
What do you want to say?
There's nothing good in a stupid woman like Amami
You just use her to release your pressure?
What has she told you?
Nothing
You're misled. You're fooled by her
No, I saw it myself
I saw what you did in the resource room
Ridiculous, filthy and psycho
Tsuboi, calm down and listen to me
No, I don't want to hear your quibbling
I just want to ask you
Listen to my explanation first
Saya Amami hates me
She's dragged you into this for revenge
Not here? Down there?
Down here
Right. Almost there
Go get that one
I got it
I was really naive
['ll manage to solve it.
I hope you'll be careful and don't be used by her
Really? She did that to you?
I'd only tell you, Shingo
Why can you tell me but not your wife?
Let's have one more round
I don't want to go home
Thanks for staying here for her til so late at night
It's okay
But your husband is really late
Maybe he's held up
Has he ever stayed overnight outside?
What're you doing? Stop it
Why can't 17
I can do what your wife and Saya did
What do you want? Calm down
I'm cool and calm
If your husband doesn't come home tonight,
can I be your lover for just 1 night?
Tsuboi
Can't|
Get the phone first
Hey
Alright. I'll be right there
My friend had a car accident
Really? You should go quickly
See you then
Manager
Can I decide where to meet Kubo Fabric?
Alright
You look good in that
Really?
You've improved a great deal
Momoko, are you bored when
Mr Hayakawa doesn't come?
Mom
Yes?
Are you getting divorced with dad?
What?
You hate dad? I can forgive dad now
I treat him coldly and he feels bad recently
I'm sorry. It's mom and dad's fault
Mom and dad love Momoko. It'll never change
You have to remember this
Good girl
- Dad
- Yes?
Do you remember what's special on this Sunday?
Sunday?
You forgot?
I remember, it's Momoko's birthday
I want to go to the zoo
I want to see the giraffe with you and mom
Alright, let's all go to the zoo
- Promise?
- Yes
Dad, go to bed
I'm almost done. I've got a big deal
Really?
Don't forget our zoo visit on Sunday
Sure
Good night
Sawako, I want to talk to you
Sorry, I'm not ready like Momoko is
Shingo, you failed today
You can't even fix a stupid woman
If you hadn't called,
I'd have succeeded
I didn't know the stupid woman would be wild
It's not yet time to intrude in both sides
Just make her fall into the trap completely
Right. What's the plan for Sunday?
What's the matter?
It's the daughter's birthday
It's said they're going to the zoo
So what?
Get the husband, and I'll take care the rest
Got it. But don't you indulge
in the fun and forget your job
Make sure you bring her to the room
There's no fun, you know women are stupid
Men are stupid
Here they are
How do you do?
I'm Kamiya of Kubo Fabric
- How do you do?
- Thank you
I am Tota
Mr Tota
Thanks for squeezing time for our meeting
Who's this lady?
She's my subordinate, Tsuboi,
who liaises with you
Ms Tsuboi, I've heard about you
Nice to meet you
Mr Kamiya, please be seated
Thank you
Mr Kamiya, make yourself at home
It'd be nice if Ms Tsuboi is serving the wine
I'm sorry, it's unthoughtful of me
I am sorry
Mr Kamiya has greatly improved
the profit of the company,
it's my honor to serve wine for you
It's thoughtful of you
No, I meant it
I -admire Mr Tota
for having a pretty and capable subordinate
Thank you
For our long term cooperation, cheers!
Cheers!
I feel optimistic about our contract
Really?
I've never seen manager being happier
Let's change a place to drink
Here you're again
Do you have time?
Yes, but
It doesn't matter
Don't touch me
Mr Kamiya
Today, CEO and GM will go to make an apology
I want to go too
Let it be settled by the company
You just do what you normally do
You're responsible for Tsuboi's behaviour
It's in the general guidelines
Me too
We'd be able to settle this
You'd better be more careful next time
Yes, sir
Tsuboi, why do you in such an outfit?
This is not a place for fun
Thanks for your caring all along,
but I can't settle for an easy way out
Stand there
Don't keep everything from me
I'm sure I can earn your trust, manager
Why can you tell me but not your wife?
(Let's meet tonight, I need to talk to you.)
You can handle it
You want to follow the step of Tsuboi?
That's enough from you
I won't forgive you. Don't hurt others any more
I won't let you get your way through here
Go back to work
Mom, I'll make him keep you company
Sorry for disturbing you for so long
I'd apologize for making you
buy a birthday gift for Momoko
It seems dad will be late tonight
But we're going to the zoo tomorrow
Really? He'll be back soon
Sorry to disturb you
If he doesn't show up, I'll forget about him
But if he comes...
['ll tell him | love him, I've been loving him.
That's enough. I won't ask for more
I just want him to know my love for him
I'm a bad mom but it's time I grew up
Dad isn't home yet?
Dad has to work. He can't help
But he promised to go to the zoo with me
Stop whining, mom will go with you
It's dad
Dad wouldn't ring the bell
Who's this?
- Sir,
What brings you here?
I might be a busy body but I do care
You woke up finally
I've been waiting
How do you feel after seeing these again?
I really resemble my mom?
You're completely different from Amami
What did you say?
You're two completely different persons
You want to resist me?
Let me go home
I need to go home to see my wife and daughter
All gone
Even if you go home, everything is gone
(Dad, we've gone to the zoo, please come.)
Stop resisting
The body is honest, anyone will do
Look...no problem
No problem
Let me go
Today is a special day
But your husband isn't home yet
Right
Would you come over to my place?
I've thought about it
Thought about what?
What happened recently, the future,
Momoko and my husband
and Mr Hayakawa
Me?
I've come up with a conclusion
I only love my husband
I still want to believe he loves me
I can't betray him
He definitely has lied to you
His love for you is only for protecting himself
All these are lies
I'm sorry
Women are stupid. They take lies in
Ridiculous
Women are ridiculous
Stop playing decent, stupid woman
Outrageous, get up
What do you want? Let go!
Come with me
- Let go!
- Stop shouting
Mr Hayakawa, stop it
Shut up, come with me
- What's this room?
- Don't ask
What're you doing?
Stop it
You admit that you're a stupid woman?
What do you want?
To teach you a lesson of course
Mr Hayakawa, please don't
Shut up and enjoy this
Stupid woman
Please let me go
Let me go home
I must go home today
Please, let me go
Look, I've got an interesting message
Sawako
What have you done to Sawako?
Why do you do this?
It has nothing to do with Sawako
I haven't done anything yet
It's just the beginning
In the secret room. It starts now
Hayakawa, are you there?
No.. Stop it.
Stop it
Please, spare Sawako
Why should I spare Sawako?
She walked in there to have fun herself
Where's Sawako now?
I can tell you but what can you do?
Please save Sawako
I told you she walked in there herself
Bring me to see Sawako. Please
You want to see your wife rotten?
Please
Alright, you may see as much as you like
Which part you want it more? Tell me
Tell me
Here.. comfortable...
Liar.. further down there
Right?
Be honest, further down there?
Down there
Down there... Alright
Good honest girl
What do you want me to do?
Look at you
I told you I only love my husband
Stop pretending. Just do what you're told
Almost time, follow me
Alright
Look
Alright. It's done
Try this
Great
Over there
At the roof?
Where's Sawako? You said I can see her
I didn't say you can see her
I said you can see as much as you can
Hey.. Hey.. Over here.
Sawako
- Let me go
- Stop it!
Don't look at me
Stop it!
You can go save her
There's a digital lock at the door
The room is locked too
Sawako
You can't save her
Take my advice and stay here to watch til the end
Stop it
Don't
Don't look at me
Don't lock at me!
Do you still trust him?
Look at him
Yes
Yes?
Hey
Are you leaving?
Should I get you a cap?
Don't touch my wife!
Shingo, what're you doing?
Why did you unlock her?
Why did you defy my order?
What're you doing, Shingo?
That's enough from you
I don't want the revenge game anymore
Outrageous!
' kill all of you!
I'm sorry, Sawako
It's all my fault
Let's go home
Outrageous!
Hey
Hey!
Are you going to fool yourself in your entire life?
He lies with his life, so I trust him
He's a liar
Let's go
It's love
We've made a mistake
1"I kil you all!
Momoko
- Momoko
Downstairs? Momoko
Momoko
Daddy, you're home finally
I'm sorry
It's itchy
Happy birthday
Stupid, why didn't you tell me
I'm sorry, Sawako
What? You've made such a mistake?
I'm really sorry. I'll do it again
Be alert
I'm sorry
Hey
You'd teach the new comers
Thank you so much
Don't stare, the same applies to you all
Go get your jobs done
I think it'd be sold at a price 500 yen higher
It's impossible with a raise of 500 yen
The same cloths are used in school uniforms
Never try never know
Let's think it over again
It's worth trying
You'd think it over again, stupid
Looking at its spinning makes me feel small
Feels like you're dragged down there too
That's too much for your imagination
How'd I make him fall madly in love with me?
Right? With cookery skills?
Cookery skills?
- Manager
- Yes?
Care for having lunch with me?
Lunch time already? Let's go
Where are we going?
Well.. Which one to go?
How about the same old place?
There's a nice one in the station
Which one? Near the west exit?
(To Tota...)
Mom, I'm leaving
I'll be fine
S&M